# Marc Hage

Web Programming Born 1980 in Heemstede



## About me

Hi, my name is Marc Hage. I've always worked with web languages. I love coding, keeping things simple and/or adhering to technical standards. I used to steer clear of javascript/ecmascript. Now it is the opposite.

Also proficient in Photoshop and to a lesser extent Illustrator

## Skills



#### Contact



marc.hage@me.com



🜎 https://marchage.github.io/





# Experience

### **Programmer**

Datling | Sendsteps | Atabix | MARC-IT since July 2006, with intermezzo's Javascript/php programmer, sometimes freelance

#### Test engineer

Sogeti July 2010 - December 2011 tester, web pen-tester.

#### Sales clerk

V & D | Perla Kantoor | Phones H'stede 1998 - 2006 Part-time sales clerk



# Education

**Bachelor of Science** 2001 - 2010 Computer science, VU Amsterdam, The Netherlands.

TMap Next July 2010 - September 2010 Includig business course at Ohio University (US).

## Projects

Running a part-time business Quaestoraat College Chaos, Typo3, PHP, HTML-CSS, Flash-**Unitas Amsterdam** ActionScript, Ubuntu, Windows, Excel. Word OSX, PhotoShop Comptroller for a 1 year term. Servicing clients' IT needs.



# Contributions

#### (None)

No worth-mentioning open source contributions https://github.com/marchage